A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller family photographs, Subseries 1005E FA1781
Rockefeller Archive Center
Winthrop Rockefeller family photographs, Subseries 1005E
1936-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Winthrop (1912-1973)
FA1781
350 Item(s) Approximately 350 images.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research.
Arrangement
As received.
Scope and Contents
Primarily consists of Winthrop Rockefeller portraits, candids, and wedding photos.
Photographs
- Winthrop Rockefeller family photographs, 1936-1973; 1005E; Approximately 350 prints
  - Prints
    - Winthrop Rockefeller family, 1936-1973; 44 prints (Box P 117)
    - Barbara Sears Rockefeller, 1948; 12 prints (Box P 162, Folder 1)
    - Barbara Sears Rockefeller - Wedding, 1948; 2 prints (Box P 162, Folder 2)
    - Jeanette Edris Rockefeller - Portraits, 8 prints (Box P 162, Folder 3)
    - Jeanette Edris Rockefeller - Portraits, 1962; 12 prints (Box P 162, Folder 4)
    - Jeanette Edris Rockefeller - Portraits - Dahl-Heim, 7 prints (Box P 162, Folder 5)
    - Jeanette Edris Rockefeller - Portraits - Hal Phyfe, 7 prints (Box P 162, Folder 6)
    - Jeanette Edris Rockefeller - Wedding, 1956; 60 prints (Box P 162, Folder 7)
    - Group Portraits - Family, 1971; 1 print (Box P 162, Folder 8)
    - Group Portraits - Family - WR and Jeanette, 1 print (Box P 162, Folder 9)
    - WR - Business - Winrock, 1 print and 2 contact sheets (Box P 162, Folder 10)
    - WR - Business - Winrock - Cattle Sale, 1958; 10 prints (Box P 162, Folder 11)
    - WR - Business - Winrock - Ten Year Anniversary Celebration, 3 prints (Box P 162, Folder 12)
    - WR - Candids - Abby Rockefeller Mauze letter to NAR, 8 prints (Box P 162, Folder 13)
    - WR - Candids - CBS "Portrait" with Harry Reasoner, 1963; 3 prints (Box P 162, Folder 14)
    - WR - Candids - Uniform, 3 prints (Box P 162, Folder 15)
    - WR - Candids - Uniform, 1941; 4 prints (Box P 162, Folder 16)
    - WR - Candids - Venezuela - AIAESD, 1950; 16 prints (Box P 162, Folder 17)
    - WR - Dignitaries - Eisenhower, 1957; 2 prints (Box P 162, Folder 18)
    - WR - Dignitaries - El Salvadorian, 2 prints (Box P 162, Folder 19)
    - WR - Dignitaries - Winston Churchill - Colonial Williamsburg, 1955; 11 prints (Box P 162, Folder 20)
    - WR - Informals, 1955; 5 prints (Box P 162, Folder 21)
    - WR - Philanthropies - Bellevue Medical Center - Chancellor Heald, 1952; 1 print (Box P 162, Folder 22)
    - WR - Portraits, 4 prints (Box P 162, Folder 23)
    - WR - Portraits, 1948 February 13; 6 prints (Box P 162, Folder 24)
    - WR - Portraits, 1953; 10 prints (Box P 162, Folder 25)
    - WR - Portraits, 1959; 8 prints (Box P 162, Folder 26)
    - WR - Portraits, 1959; 18 prints (Box P 162, Folder 27)
    - WR - Portraits, 1965; 6 prints (Box P 162, Folder 28)
    - WR - Portraits, 1967; 3 prints (Box P 162, Folder 29)
    - WR - Portraits - Bob Hope Show, 1973; 30 prints (Box P 162, Folder 30)
    - WR - Portraits - Miscellaneous, 1950s-1960s; 15 prints (Box P 162, Folder 31)
    - WR - Portraits - Vogue Studio, 12 prints (Box P 162, Folder 32)
  - Albums
    - Jeanette Edris Wedding, 1956; 12 prints (Box A 45)
  - Oversized
    - Winthrop Rockefeller - Portraits, 2 prints (Box O 36)
    - Winthrop Rockefeller - Portraits (Box C 4)